articlesbay.org 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy - ArticlesBay.org

ArticlesBay.org designed its privacy policy to demonstrate its commitment to fair practice. Following are the kind of information which we collect and adhere to strict privacy standards.

## Use of Cookies:

ArticlesBay.org used cookie system for its login sessions, this means your browser sets a "cookie" maintain your login session on your computer. If you choose to remember your password on your computer the this cookie will be created for a period of one year and will automatically expire after one year and if you do not wish to maintain this cookie then please uncheck the option "Remember me" while login, the cookie will get destroyed after you close the browser.

## Use of IP Address:

ArticlesBay.org does not store or maintain your computers IP address.

## Use of Email & Other Personal Details:

ArticlesBay.org records users name, email and password for future login purpose and we will never sell, rent or disclose to any third party without your consent.

## Content Liability & Filtering:

ArticlesBay.org do everything possible to maintain strict content guidelines and use intelligent filter to filter non-appropriate, abusive, racial and adult words, we can not be held liable for any offence, damage, injury or other legal infraction attributed to such content. ArticlesBay.org is a service provider; we are not content provider.

## Use of Ads:

ArticlesBay.org partners with various ads systems from time to time; this will not affect your service or rights in any manner. Language, banners, text, URL's, graphics displayed on these Ad systems are not owned or maintained by ArticlesBay.org therefore we are not responsible for any such content which displayed ads owned by these ad systems.

Also we use **third-party advertising** (like [Google Adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense/)) to serve ads when you visit our Web site pages. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to show ads based on their visit and interest in subject available on our site. If you would like to opt out of the DART cookie, check the method on [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Please note that these companies may use collected information (not including any of your personal details) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements of your interest. Looking for more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Changes:

ArticlesBay.org's privacy policy changes time to time and changes are posted on privacy policy page of ArticlesBay.org, so please check back often to check for changes in ArticlesBay.org's privacy policy. 

ARTICLESBAY.ORG IS A FREE ARTICLES HOSTING WEBSITE, WE DO NOT PROVIDE OR SUPPORT ANY LEGAL CONSIQUENCES AND ANY PARTY IN ANY MANNER. IF YOU ARE NOT AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY THEN WE REQUEST YOU NOT TO CREATE ACCOUNT OR POST ARTICLES OR POST COMMENTS ON ARTICLESBAY.ORG

If you still have question about ArticlesBay.org's privacy policy then please contact us. 

* * *
